A Guide to the R. Bruce Merrifield papers, Rockefeller University Faculty FA415
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Laboratory Files, 4
  - Administration
    - Lab Budgets, 1970-1980 (Box 139, Folder 947)
    - Lab Manual (Box 139, Folder 948)
    - Lab Relocation, 1997 (Box 140, Folder 949)
    - Lab Reports, 1987; 1989; 1992-1996 (Box 140, Folder 950)
      - Disk, 2016:FA415:003 (Box 140, Folder 950)
    - Lab Safety (Box 140, Folder 951-953)
    - Laboratory Animal Research Center (LARC) (Box 140, Folder 954)
    - Laboratory Budget, 1992-1993 (Box 140, Folder 955)
    - Laboratory Business, Undated; 1981; 1985; 1992 (Box 140, Folder 956-958)
    - Laboratory Report, 1991; 1993-1995 (Box 140, Folder 959-961)
    - Laboratory Reports, 1969-1986 (Box 140, Folder 962-964)
    - Laboratory Safety and Remodeling (Nichols, Gershey, Sauers) (Box 141, Folder 965)
    - Lu, Gui-shen (Box 141, Folder 966)
    - Lyons, O'Donnell Correspondence, etc., 1987-1990 (Box 141, Folder 967)
    - Macaulay, William (Box 141, Folder 968)
    - Macaulay, William (Box 141, Folder 968A)
    - Martin, Lenore (Box 141, Folder 969-970)
    - Martin, Lenore (Box 141, Folder 970A)
    - Merrifield Lab Summary Report, 2004-2006 (Box 142, Folder 971)
    - Merrifield Laboratory, 1968 (Box 142, Folder 972)
    - "Methylene Chloride" (Box 142, Folder 973)
    - Mitchell, Alex (Box 142, Folder 974)
    - Mitchell, Alex (Box 142, Folder 974A)
    - Mitchell, Scott (Box 142, Folder 975)
    - Mojsov, Svetlana (Box 142, Folder 976-977)
    - Mojsov, Svetlana (Box 142, Folder 977A)
    - Naayem, Lucy, Inventory (Box 142, Folder 978)
    - Navy, 1987 (Box 142, Folder 979)
    - New Appointment Request, Anagani (Box 142, Folder 980)
    - New Laboratories, Flexner 403, 404, 405 (Box 142, Folder 981)
    - NIH Grant (DK24039-21-25), Glucagon, 1998-1999 (Box 143, Folder 982)
    - Novo Norodisk (Box 143, Folder 983)
    - Operating Instructions for Type 20 Rotary Valves and Model VDU-20 Valve Drive Unit (Box 143, Folder 984)
    - Peptide Inventory, Scott Mitchell, 1992 (Box 143, Folder 985)
    - Personnel (Box 143, Folder 986-987)
    - Personnel Files, A (Box 144, Folder 988)
      Anaya Andreu Asato
    - Personnel Files, A (Box 144, Folder 988A)
    - Personnel Files, B (Box 144, Folder 989)
      Bach Berg Bhargava Bouvier
    - Personnel Files, B (Box 144, Folder 989A)
    - Personnel Files, Barany (Box 144, Folder 990-992, Box 145, Folder 993-994)
    - Personnel Files, Barany (Box 145, Folder 994A)
    - Personnel Files, C (Box 145, Folder 995-996)
      Caldi Chandramouli Cheung Chowdhury Christensen Clavijo Cosand Cox Cunningham
    - Personnel Files, C (Box 146, Folder 996A)
    - Personnel Files, D (Box 146, Folder 997-998)
      Dauphin Defoort Didolkar DiMarchi Dong Doscher Drain Draper
    - Personnel Files, D (Box 146, Folder 998A)
    - Personnel Files, E (Box 146, Folder 999)
      Eskeland Engelhard
    - Personnel Files, E (Box 146, Folder 999A)
    - Personnel Files, Erickson (Box 146, Folder 1000-1001, Box 147, Folder 1002-1003)
    - Personnel Files, Erickson (Box 147, Folder 1003A)
    - Personnel Files, F (Box 147, Folder 1004, Box 148, Folder 1005)
      Fan Feinberg Felix Fink Fitzpatrick Fleischer Floyd Fook Fox Franchini
    - Personnel Files, F (Box 148, Folder 1005A)
    - Personnel Files, G (Box 148, Folder 1006-1007, Box 149, Folder 1008)
      Galantino Galardy Gisin Goissis Gurzenda Gutte
    - Personnel Files, G (Box 149, Folder 1008A)
    - Personnel Files, H (Box 149, Folder 1009)
      Hampton Haser Hew Holm Huang, L. Huang, W.
    - Personnel Files, H (Box 149, Folder 1009A)
    - Personnel Files, Hetnarski (Box 149, Folder 1010, Box 150, Folder 1011)
    - Personnel Files, Hetnarski (Box 150, Folder 1011A)
    - Personnel Files, Hodges (Box 150, Folder 1012-1013)
    - Personnel Files, Hodges (Box 150, Folder 1013A)
    - Personnel Files, I (Box 150, Folder 1014)
      Isaac Isied Iwasa Izumi
    - Personnel Files, I (Box 151, Folder 1014A)
    - Personnel Files, J (Box 151, Folder 1015)
      Johnson
    - Personnel Files, K (Box 151, Folder 1016-1017)
      Kagan Kaiser Ke Kendall Khan Kolodin Koul Krieger Krug Kubiak
    - Personnel Files, K (Box 151, Folder 1018)
    - Personnel Files, Kaiser Lab (Box 151, Folder 1019-1020)
    - Personnel Files, Kaiser Lab (Box 152, Folder 1020A-1020B)
    - Personnel Files, Kent (Box 152, Folder 1021-1022)
    - Personnel Files, Kent (Box 152, Folder 1022A)
    - Personnel Files, L (Box 153, Folder 1023-1025)
      Levine Levit Lewis Li Lin Lindsey Liu, C. Liu, W. Loudon Lu, G. Lu, W.
    - Personnel Files, L (Box 153, Folder 1025A-1025B)
    - Personnel Files, M (Box 153, Folder 1026, Box 154, Folder 1027-1030)
      Macaulay Macdonald McNichol Makov Marglin Marshall Martin Meyer-Glauner Miller Mitchell Murphy
    - Personnel Files, M (Box 154, Folder 1030A, Box 155, Folder 1030B)
    - Personnel Files, N (Box 155, Folder 1031)
      Najjar Nardelli Ng
    - Personnel Files, N (Box 155, Folder 1031A)
    - Personnel Files, P (Box 155, Folder 1032)
      Pieczenik Pileggi
    - Personnel Files, P (Box 155, Folder 1032A)
    - Personnel Files, R (Box 155, Folder 1033-1034)
      Ragnarsson Rao Ray Riemen Robinson Rosberger Rosenzweig Rotondi Ryabtsev
    - Personnel Files, R (Box 155, Folder 1034A)
    - Personnel Files, S (Box 155, Folder 1035-1036)
      Sadarangani Sang Sapse Sharma Shen Singer Slotboom Spetzler Steel Stewart
    - Personnel Files, S (Box 155, Folder 1036A)
    - Personnel Files, T (Box 155, Folder 1037-1038)
      Tam Teplan Tjoeng Tuan
    - Personnel Files, T (Box 156, Folder 1038A)
    - Personnel Files, U (Box 156, Folder 1039)
      Unson
    - Personnel Files, V (Box 156, Folder 1040)
      Vizioli Volin Voss Vunnam
    - Personnel Files, V (Box 156, Folder 1040A)
    - Personnel Files, W (Box 156, Folder 1041-1043, Box 157, Folder 1044-1045)
      Waase Wang, C. Wang, D. Wang, S. Weinberg Whitney Wong Wood Woolley Wu
    - Personnel Files, W (Box 157, Folder 1045A)
    - Personnel Files, Y (Box 157, Folder 1046)
      Yang Ye Yoo Yoshida
    - Personnel Files, Y (Box 157, Folder 1046A)
    - Personnel Files, Z (Box 157, Folder 1047)
      Zhang Zhao
    - Personnel Files, Z (Box 157, Folder 1047A)
    - Progress Report, 1991 (Box 157, Folder 1048)
    - Quarterly Effort Reports, 1968-1978 (Box 157, Folder 1049)
    - Reproductive Biology Grant (Box 157, Folder 1050)
    - Riemen, Mark (Box 158, Folder 1051)
    - Riemen, Mark (Box 158, Folder 1051A)
    - Rough Drafts of Grants, 1983 (Box 158, Folder 1052)
    - RU Accounting Reports, FY1985-1991 (Box 158, Folder 1053)
    - Safety Manual, 1982 (Box 158, Folder 1054)
    - Sakmar-Unson Grant Application, 1997-1998 (Box 158, Folder 1055)
    - Sapse, Anne-Marie (Box 158, Folder 1056)
    - Sapse, Anne-Marie (Box 158, Folder 1056A)
    - Sarin, Virender (Box 158, Folder 1057)
    - Sarin, Virender (Box 158, Folder 1057A)
    - Shai, Yechiel (Box 158, Folder 1058)
      - Disk, 2016:FA415:004 (Box 158, Folder 1058)
    - Shai, Yechiel (Box 158, Folder 1058A)
    - SPPS Protocols and MWs (Box 158, Folder 1059)
    - Tam Grant (Box 159, Folder 1060)
    - Tam, James (Box 159, Folder 1061-1063)
    - Tam, James (Box 159, Folder 1063A)
    - Technicians (Box 159, Folder 1064)
    - Uhrik v. Rockefeller (Box 160, Folder 1065)
    - US-Spain Grant (Box 160, Folder 1066)
    - Unson, Cecilia (Box 160, Folder 1067-1068)
    - Unson, Cecilia (Box 160, Folder 1068A)
    - Unson Grant Application (Box 161, Folder 1069)
    - US Public Health Research Fellowships (Box 161, Folder 1070)
    - Vunnam, Satyanarayana (Box 161, Folder 1071)
    - Vunnam, Satyanarayana (Box 161, Folder 1071A)
    - Wade, David (Box 161, Folder 1072-1074)
      - Disk, 2016:FA415:005 (Box 161, Folder 1074)
    - Wade, David (Box 162, Folder 1074A)
    - Wang, Su Sun (Box 162, Folder 1075)
    - Yang, Yan (Box 162, Folder 1076)
    - Yoshida, Makoto (Box 162, Folder 1077)
    - Yoshida, Makoto (Box 162, Folder 1077A)
    - Zaia, Dimas (Box 162, Folder 1078-1078A)
    - Zaia, Dimas (Box 162, Folder 1078A)
  - Notes and Notebooks
    - ? (Equilibrium Dialysis) (Box 162, Folder 1079)
    - -Ala-NO2-Arg, 1970 (Box 162, Folder 1080)
    - III, "Infrared", 1958 (Box 162, Folder 1081)
    - AA Chromatograms: Ala-Arg Run (Tryps Dig., etc.), 1970 (Box 162, Folder 1082)
    - AAA, 1966; 1969 (Box 163, Folder 1083-1084)
    - Aminomethylation of Polystyrene, Beers (Box 163, Folder 1085)
    - Abbas, No. 1, 2007 (Box 163, Folder 1086)
    - Abbas, No. 2, 2007-2008 (Box 163, Folder 1087)
    - Abbas, No. 3, 2008 (Box 163, Folder 1088)
    - Abbas, No. 4, 2008 (Box 163, Folder 1089)
    - Abbas, No. 5, 2008 (Box 164, Folder 1090)
    - ACAAI, Recent Analyses (Box 164, Folder 1091)
    - ACAAII, Recent Analyses (Box 164, Folder 1092)
    - Acid Cleavage of Urethanes and Esters (Box 164, Folder 1093)
    - ACTIAI, Trypsin Inhibitor Assays (Box 164, Folder 1094)
    - Ala10Val Notes (Box 164, Folder 1095)
    - Alexander, 1992 (Box 164, Folder 1096)
    - Amino Acid Analyses #3 (Box 164, Folder 1097)
    - Amino Acid Analyses and Peptide Sequencing (Box 164, Folder 1098)
    - Amino Acid Analyzer Data, 1981-1983 (Box 165, Folder 1099)
    - Angiotensinyl-Bradykinin (Box 165, Folder 1100)
    - Assays, 1987-1989 (Box 165, Folder 1101-1103)
    - Auto Radiograph Data (Box 166, Folder 1104)
    - Bach, No. 1, October 1968 (Box 166, Folder 1105)
    - Bach, No. 2, June 1970 (Box 166, Folder 1106)
    - Bach, No. 3, June 1971 (Box 166, Folder 1107)
    - Bach, No. 4, June 1972 (Box 167, Folder 1108)
    - Bach, No. 5, May 1973 (Box 167, Folder 1109)
    - Bach, No. 6, "Tetradecapeptide Synthesis, Schiff Base Montoring," 1974 (Box 167, Folder 1110)
    - Bach, No. 7, "Monitoring with Imidazolium Picrate," May 1974 (Box 167, Folder 1111)
    - Bach, No. 8, November 1974 (Box 167, Folder 1112)
    - Bach, No. 9, May 1975 (Box 167, Folder 1113)
    - Bach, No. 10, October 1975 (Box 168, Folder 1114)
    - Bach, No. 11, May 1976 (Box 168, Folder 1115)
    - Bach, No. 12, February 1977 (Box 168, Folder 1116)
    - Bach, No. 13, March 1976 (Box 168, Folder 1117)
    - Bach, No. 13, July 1977 (Box 168, Folder 1118)
    - Bach, No. 14, November 1977 (Box 168, Folder 1119)
    - Bach, No. 15, April 1978 (Box 169, Folder 1120)
    - Bach, Amino Acid Analyses, 1970 (Box 169, Folder 1121)
    - Batarags, No. 1, 1982 (Box 169, Folder 1122)
    - Batarags, No. 2, 1982 (Box 169, Folder 1123)
    - Best Procedure for Each Step, 1997 (Box 169, Folder 1124)
    - Bhavani, No. 1, June 1997 (Box 169, Folder 1125)
    - Bhavani, No. 2 (Box 169, Folder 1126)
    - Breslow, Neurophysin (Box 170, Folder 1127)
    - Calc pA2 Values (Box 170, Folder 1128)
    - "Calculations for Specific Radioactivity after Synthesis" (Box 170, Folder 1129)
    - Caldi, 1971 (Box 170, Folder 1130)
    - CD Data (Box 170, Folder 1131)
    - Cecropin and HPLC Data (Box 170, Folder 1132)
    - Cecropin and Magainin, 1989 (Box 170, Folder 1133)
    - Cecropin Data (Box 171, Folder 1134)
    - "CFM and Merrifield / Chromatofocusing", 1983 (Box 171, Folder 1135)
    - Chandramouli, 2004 (Box 171, Folder 1136)
    - Chemical Problems, 1971-1972 (Box 171, Folder 1137)
    - Chemistry: Notes, Plans, Directions, etc. (Box 171, Folder 1138)
    - Cheung, Binder, Cloning, 1994-1996 (Box 171, Folder 1139)
    - Cheung, Binder, ECL, 1994-1995 (Box 172, Folder 1140)
    - Cheung, Binder, Sequences, 1993-1996 (Box 172, Folder 1141)
    - Cheung, Connie, Lab Experiments (Box 172, Folder 1142-1143, Box 173, Folder 1144-1147, Box 174, Folder 1148)
    - Cheung, No. 1, 1994 (Box 174, Folder 1149)
    - Chlorobenzyl Resin, 1974-1975 (Box 174, Folder 1150)
    - Chromatograms on New Met-o Expts. and Sulfonium Expt., April 1983 (Box 174, Folder 1151)
    - Clarke, No. 1, August 1970 (Box 174, Folder 1152)
    - Clarke, No. 2, March 1971 (Box 174, Folder 1153)
    - Clarke, No. 3, July 1971 (Box 175, Folder 1154)
    - Clarke, No. 4, March 1972 (Box 175, Folder 1155)
    - Clarke, No. 5, September 1972 (Box 175, Folder 1156)
    - Clarke, No. 6, June 1973 (Box 175, Folder 1157)
    - Cohen, No. 12, "Peptides," June 1968 (Box 175, Folder 1158)
    - Cohen, No. 13, February 1969 (Box 175, Folder 1159)
    - Cohen, No. 14, October 1969 (Box 175, Folder 1160)
    - Cohen, No. 15, March 1970 (Box 175, Folder 1161)
    - Combinatorial Data (Box 176, Folder 1162)
    - Conductivity Charts and Data, Wade (Box 176, Folder 1163)
    - Copies of Ellen's Bining and cAMP Assays (Box 176, Folder 1164)
    - Coupling Rates (Box 176, Folder 1165)
    - CP-I Data (Box 176, Folder 1166)
    - CPI Data (Box 176, Folder 1167)
    - Cunningham, No. 1, August 1987 (Box 176, Folder 1168)
    - Cunningham, No. 2, October 1988 (Box 176, Folder 1169)
    - Cunningham, No. 3, August 1989 (Box 177, Folder 1170)
    - Cunningham, No. 4, October 1990 (Box 177, Folder 1171)
    - Cunningham, No. 4, "Plastocyamin" (Box 177, Folder 1172)
    - Cunningham, No. 5, "Plastocyanin," 1990 (Box 178, Folder 1173)
    - Curanovi, 2002 (Box 178, Folder 1174)
    - Current Experimental Data and Ideas, 1972 (Box 178, Folder 1175)
    - Current Experiments (Box 178, Folder 1176)
    - Data, 1997-1998 (Box 178, Folder 1177)
    - Data on Synthesis and Act of CecropinA.B.D (Box 178, Folder 1178)
    - de Lencastre, 1994 (Box 178, Folder 1179)
    - Diffusion Data (Box 179, Folder 1180)
    - Di Marchi Notebook, Interferon (Box 179, Folder 1181)
    - D.L.-Standards # RSF, 1971 July (Box 179, Folder 1182)
    - DNA Sequences 1, 1998-2000 (Box 179, Folder 1183)
    - DNA Sequences 2, 1999-2005 (Box 179, Folder 1184)
    - DNA Sequences 3, 2000-2001 (Box 180, Folder 1185)
    - DNA Sequences 4, 2000-2001 (Box 180, Folder 1186)
    - DNA Sequences 5, 2002-2003 (Box 181, Folder 1187)
    - DNA Sequences 6, 2003 (Box 181, Folder 1188)
    - DNA Sequences 7, 2004-2005; 2007 (Box 182, Folder 1189-1190)
    - DNA Sequences 8, 2005-2006 (Box 182, Folder 1191, Box 183, Folder 1192)
    - DNA Sequences 9, 2005-2007 (Box 183, Folder 1193-1194)
    - DNA Sequences 10, 2007 (Box 183, Folder 1195, Box 184, Folder 1196)
    - DNA Sequences 11, 2008-2009 (Box 184, Folder 1197-1198)
    - Durrah, Tracy (Box 184, Folder 1199)
    - Durrah, No. 1, 1988-1989 (Box 185, Folder 1200-1201)
    - Durrah, No. 2, 1989-1990 (Box 185, Folder 1202, Box 186, Folder 1203)
    - Durrah, No. 3, 1989-1990 (Box 186, Folder 1204)
    - Dusica Tether, 2002-2003 (Box 186, Folder 1205-1206)
    - Ellen's File (Box 186, Folder 1207)
    - Ellen's Protocols, 1984-1990 (Box 187, Folder 1208)
    - ELM, "Columns and Bioassays on Sarin's Cys 1-155 Pept.," September 1982 (Box 187, Folder 1209)
    - ELM, "Columns, SC15 to SC36," February 1983 (Box 187, Folder 1210)
    - Emil (Box 187, Folder 1211)
    - Emil, Armour Laboratories (Box 187, Folder 1212)
    - "Enzyme Digest, ME...Series" (Box 187, Folder 1213)
    - "Enymatic Digestions of Serine 1-166 and Cys 1-166 IFN1," April 1982 (Box 188, Folder 1214)
    - Equations (Box 188, Folder 1215)
    - Experimental Notes (Box 188, Folder 1216-1217)
    - Feinberg, No. 1, November 1969 (Box 188, Folder 1218)
    - Feinberg, No. 2, May 1970 (Box 188, Folder 1219)
    - Feinberg, No. 3, September 1970 (Box 188, Folder 1220)
    - Feinberg, No. 4, April 1971 (Box 189, Folder 1221)
    - Feinberg, No. 5, September 1972 (Box 189, Folder 1222)
    - Feinberg, No. 6, April 1973 (Box 189, Folder 1223)
    - Feinberg, No. 7, January 1975 (Box 189, Folder 1224)
    - Fink, No. 1, January 1987 (Box 190, Folder 1225)
    - Fink, No. 2, August 1987 (Box 190, Folder 1226)
    - Fitzpatrick, Kevin, Lab Experiments (Box 190, Folder 1227-1228, Box 191, Folder 1229-1231)
    - Fitzpatrick, No. 1, 1991 (Box 191, Folder 1232)
    - Fitzpatrick, No. 2, 1992 (Box 192, Folder 1233)
    - Fitzpatrick, No. 3, 1993 (Box 192, Folder 1234)
    - Fleischer, No. 1, 1990-1991 (Box 192, Folder 1235-1237)
    - Fleischer and Sadarangani, No. 1A, 1991 (Box 193, Folder 1238)
    - Floyd - Seminar Notes, 1984-1985 (Box 193, Folder 1239)
    - Formula and Calculation of LC Values (Box 193, Folder 1240)
    - Formyl Trp Problem, Wade and Andreu (Box 193, Folder 1241)
    - Fox, "Biological Methods from Floyd Fox" (Box 193, Folder 1242)
    - Freiberg, "Optical Purity, BoC-419," No. 2 (Box 193, Folder 1243)
    - Future Experiments, 1957-1959 (Box 193, Folder 1244)
    - Glucagon, D-peptides, Libby (Box 193, Folder 1245)
    - Glucagon, Notes, Plans, Ideas (Box 193, Folder 1246)
    - Glucagon Slides and Tables, Summaries of Data (Box 193, Folder 1247)
    - Gly-Val-Resin Problem (Box 194, Folder 1248)
    - GR Expression, 2003 (Box 194, Folder 1249)
    - Grove, No. 1, September 1959 (Box 194, Folder 1250)
    - Hazra, TPCB Laboratory Rotation, 2005 (Box 194, Folder 1251)
    - Heath, No. 3, C409 Hemoglobin Semisynthesis, 1979-1980 (Box 194, Folder 1252)
    - Hodges, September 1973 (Box 195, Folder 1253)
    - Hodges, "DIEA Reaction with CH2O2 as Observed via Formation of Corresponding Picrate" (Box 195, Folder 1254)
    - Ideas for Us (Box 195, Folder 1255)
    - Incomplete Coupling Experiment, Boc-Leu-Ala Res., 1970 (Box 195, Folder 1256)
    - Influence of Concentrations of Reagents upon Kinetic Results (Box 195, Folder 1257)
    - Insulin (Box 195, Folder 1258)
    - Inventories and Assay Data on Hybrids (Box 195, Folder 1259)
    - IR (Box 195, Folder 1260)
    - IR, Tam (Box 195, Folder 1261)
    - Isaac, No. 1, September 1984 (Box 195, Folder 1262)
    - Isaac, No. 2, December 1984 (Box 196, Folder 1263)
    - Isaac, No. 3, March 1985 (Box 196, Folder 1264)
    - Isaac, No. 4, August 1985 (Box 196, Folder 1265)
    - Issac, No. 5, November 1985 (Box 196, Folder 1266)
    - Isaac, No. 6, February 1986 (Box 196, Folder 1267)
    - Iwasa, 1987 (Box 196, Folder 1268)
    - Iwasa, No. 1, 1987 (Box 197, Folder 1269)
    - Iwasa, No. 2, 1988 (Box 197, Folder 1270)
    - Iwasa, No. 3, 1988 (Box 197, Folder 1271)
    - Juvvadi, No. 8, "Bioassay in Dr. Merrifield's Lab," August 1994 (Box 197, Folder 1272)
    - Juvvadi, Vunnam, and E. Merrifield, 1995 (Box 197, Folder 1273)
    - Kaiser (Box 197, Folder 1274, Box 198, Folder 1275-1277)
    - Kaiser, 1983-1984 (Box 198, Folder 1278)
    - Kaiser, 1984 (Box 199, Folder 1279)
    - Kaiser, 1993 (Box 199, Folder 1280)
    - Kaiser, 1993-1994 (Box 199, Folder 1281)
    - Kaiser, Angiotensin (Box 199, Folder 1282)
    - Kaiser, Cecropin Synthesis (Box 199, Folder 1283)
    - Kaiser, Data, 1988 (Box 199, Folder 1284)
    - Kaiser, For Poster, 1987 (Box 199, Folder 1285)
    - Kaiser, HPLC (Box 199, Folder 1286)
    - Kaiser, Magainin Sciences (Box 199, Folder 1287)
    - Kaiser, NMR Paper, 1991 (Box 200, Folder 1288)
    - Kaiser, Tetrahedron Letters, 1987 (Box 200, Folder 1289)
    - Kelmanovich, June 2000 (Box 200, Folder 1290)
    - Kent, Coupling Eff. (Box 200, Folder 1291)
    - Kent, "Optical Purities," November 1975 (Box 200, Folder 1292)
    - Kinetics (Box 200, Folder 1293)
    - Kinetics, BPOC Rate Monitoring (Box 200, Folder 1294)
    - Kinetics of Boc-Val-OCH2 Resin Deprotection (Box 201, Folder 1295)
    - Kolodin, 1988 (Box 201, Folder 1296)
    - Kreiger, "Assays," July 1976 (Box 201, Folder 1297)
    - LC vs. MIC Assay Data (Box 201, Folder 1298)
    - L-RNase, Martin (Box 201, Folder 1299)
    - Levine, No. 1, April 1969 (Box 201, Folder 1300)
    - Levine, No. 2, January 1970 (Box 201, Folder 1301)
    - Levine, "Monitor Charts", 1969 (Box 201, Folder 1302)
    - Li, No. 1, "Solid Phase Synthesis," January 1985 (Box 202, Folder 1303)
    - Li, No. 2, "Solid-Phase Synthesis," September 1985 (Box 202, Folder 1304)
    - Li, No. 2, "Solid-Phase Synthesis," September 1985 (Box 202, Folder 1304)
    - Li, No. 3, "Solid-Phase Synthesis" (Box 202, Folder 1305)
    - Li, No. 4, "Solid-Phase Synthesis," June 1986 (Box 202, Folder 1306)
    - Li, No. 5, December 1986 (Box 202, Folder 1307)
    - L.V., No. 3, June 1981 (Box 203, Folder 1308)
    - L.V., No. 4, February 1982 (Box 203, Folder 1309)
    - L.V., No. 5, September 1982 (Box 203, Folder 1310)
    - Lu, Gui-shen Data (Box 204, Folder 1311)
    - Lucy, Met(O) (Box 204, Folder 1312)
    - Macauley, No. 1, June 1986 (Box 204, Folder 1313)
    - Macauley, No. 1, July 1986 (Box 204, Folder 1314)
    - Macauley, No. 2, February 1987 (Box 204, Folder 1315)
    - Macauley, No. 2, "CD Spec.," 1987 (Box 204, Folder 1316)
    - Macauley, No. 3, September 1987 (Box 205, Folder 1317)
    - Macdonald, Doug, Lab Experiments (Box 205, Folder 1318-1319, Box 206, Folder 1320-1323)
    - Macdonald, No. 1, 1989 (Box 207, Folder 1324)
    - Macdonald, No. 2, 1989-1990 (Box 207, Folder 1325)
    - Macdonald, No. 3, 1990 (Box 207, Folder 1326)
    - Macdonald, No. 4, 1990-1991 (Box 207, Folder 1327)
    - Manuscript (Box 207, Folder 1328)
    - Martin, No. 1, November 1988 (Box 207, Folder 1329)
    - Martin, No. 2, January 1989 (Box 208, Folder 1330)
    - Martin, No. 3, January 1989 (Box 208, Folder 1331)
    - Martin, No. 4, February 1989 (Box 208, Folder 1332)
    - Martin, No. 5, May 1989 (Box 208, Folder 1333)
    - Martin, No. 6, May 1990 (Box 208, Folder 1334)
    - Martin, No. 7, May 1991 (Box 208, Folder 1335)
    - Martin, No. 8, January 1992 (Box 209, Folder 1336)
    - Martin, No. 9, June 1993 (Box 209, Folder 1337)
    - Martin, "RNase," September 1979 (Box 209, Folder 1338)
    - Mass Spec on CH2Cl2 also LAGV and Purification (Box 209, Folder 1339)
    - Mass Spectrometer Results, 1986-1987 (Box 209, Folder 1340-1341)
    - Matheis, No. 1, 1984 (Box 210, Folder 1342)
    - Matheis, No. 2, 1984-1985 (Box 210, Folder 1343)
    - Matheis, No. 3, 1984-1985 (Box 210, Folder 1344)
    - Matheis, No. 4, 1985-1986 (Box 210, Folder 1345)
    - Matheis-Gurzenda, No. 5, 1986 (Box 211, Folder 1346)
    - Matheis-Gurzenda, No. 6, 1986-1987 (Box 211, Folder 1347)
    - Matheis-Gurzenda, No. 7, 1987 (Box 211, Folder 1348)
    - Matheis-Gurzenda, No. 8, 1987-1988 (Box 211, Folder 1349)
    - Matheis-Gurzenda, No. 9, 1988 (Box 212, Folder 1350)
    - "MC300 Series 3rd Workup of IF1Cus1", 1984 April (Box 212, Folder 1351)
    - "MC300 Series HPLC Analysis, Phenyl-(NH4)2 SO4", 1985 February (Box 212, Folder 1352)
    - "MC 311", 1984 September (Box 212, Box 1353)
    - ME 304, 1981 (Box 212, Folder 1354)
    - Melittin Analogs (Box 212, Folder 1355)
    - Merrifield, 1945 (Box 212, Folder 1356)
    - "Merrifield", 1981 (Box 212, Folder 1357)
    - Merrifield-II, 7-18, 1981 September (Box 213, Folder 1358)
    - Merrifield-II, (ME7), 1981 October (Box 213, Folder 1359)
    - Merrifield, Excerpts from Nos. 311, 334, 1955 (Box 213, Folder 1360)
    - "The Merrifield Machine 'Manual'" (Box 213, Folder 1361)
    - Merrifield, "New Experiments, Ideas, Notes", 1958 (Box 213, Folder 1362)
    - Merrifield, No. 1, "CD, Glucagon," September 1985 (Box 213, Folder 1363)
    - Merrifield, No. 219, "Yeast," September 1944 (Box 213, Folder 1364)
    - Merrifield, No. 231, "Pyrimidines," July 1947 (Box 213, Folder 1365)
    - Merrifield, No. 251, "Purines-Microbiol.," February 1946 (Box 214, Folder 1366)
    - Merrifield, No. 263, "Purines - Microbiology," July 1946 (Box 214, Folder 1367)
    - Merrifield, No. 301, "Pyrimidines," October 1948 (Box 214, Folder 1368)
    - Merrifield, No. 302, April 1951 (Box 214, Folder 1369)
    - Merrifield, No. 303, November 1951 (Box 214, Folder 1370)
    - Merrifield, No. 304, March 1952 (Box 214, Folder 1371)
    - Merrifield, No. 304, March 1952 (Box 214, Folder 1371)
    - Merrifield, No. 305, November 1952 (Box 214, Folder 1372)
    - Merrifield, No. 306, April 1953 (Box 214, Folder 1373)
    - Merrifield, No. 307, September 1953 (Box 214, Folder 1374)
    - Merrifield, No. 308, February 1954 (Box 214, Folder 1375)
    - Merrifield, No. 309, September 1954 (Box 215, Folder 1376)